Contact

garimaluthra2198@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/garima-luthra (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Database Management System (DBMS)

C++

Web Development

Honors-Awards

Scholar

Scholar

NASA Space settlement design Contest, Winner

Best Mentor

Garima Luthra

Site Reliability Engineering intern @LinkedIn | Mentor, Skillship Foundation | Team Lead, Instinct Delhi

Summary

I am a third year undergraduate pursuing computer science engineering at Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for women and currently working as a Site Reliability Engineering intern at LinkedIn. I am an experienced core team lead and an avid learner in technology, always curious to learn new things.

Experience

LinkedIn Site Reliability Engineering intern May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months)

SkillShip Foundation

Mentor

February 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

- Mentored a group of mentees in the Cod{on}fest 2020 to help and guide them in the field of competitive programming.
- Taught the mentees various concepts, helped them find optimised solutions to problems and debugged their codes.
- Selected as one of the top three mentors in the program for actively helping the students.
- Helped in creating programming contests on CodeChef.

LinkedIn Inbassador February 2020 - March 2020 (2 months)

WooTech Mentee December 2019 - January 2020 (2 months)

- Built an IMDb scrapper in python using the beautiful soup library.
- Used the smtplib module to send mails to the users which contained timings of their favourite shows.

Instinct- Peer Educator's and Life skills society of IGDTUW Core Team Lead

2017 - November 2019 (2 years)

- Instinct- Peer Educator's Society of IGDTUW aims to help the students within the college to discover their passion and to mould themselves into becoming stronger individuals.
- Conducted sessions and peer discussions on confidence building, public speaking and introspection.
- Actively organised many technical sessions in the college under the Women Hacks wing.

eDC IIT Delhi(Entrepreneurship Development Cell)

Campus Ambassador

August 2018 - March 2019 (8 months)

Liaised with the E-cell coordinators of IIT Delhi

to promote entrepreneurship activities among the students of IGDTUW.

Innerve

Head coordinator

August 2018 - October 2018 (3 months)

Rendezvous IITD

Campus Ambassador

August 2018 - October 2018 (3 months)

Synergy Igdtuw

Event management coordinator

August 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Taarangana

Creative Coordinator

September 2017 - February 2018 (6 months)

Ryan International School

Student Council minister

March 2014 - March 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Education

INDIRA GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY FOR WOMEN

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Ryan International School - India

· (2002 - 2016)